accessplace.com 2014-06-18

# AccessPlace privacy policy, personal user data, third party sites, children and user consent

## Privacy

At AccessPlace we respect the privacy of our users and follow a strict privacy policy. This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information which we may receive via the web site located at AccessPlace, and is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details. Be assured that the information you share with AccessPlace is kept strictly confidential and fully secure, and that AccessPlace will never misuse this information.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for AccessPlace. 

## Personal User Data

The only ways in which AccessPlace may receive Personally Identifiable Information about you is if you knowingly and willingly provide the information by contacting us using email or through one of our service areas, including, but not limited to, contests and promotions. In such areas, the information you disclose is done so knowingly and willingly, at your sole discretion. The Personally Identifiable Information you disclose is optional, and is normally required so as to effectively enter you into any contest we may offer or to reply to your email and correspondence. 

If you give us permission to use your email address and name we are not responsible for any correspondence that you may receive. We do not sell or compile lists of email addresses for marketing purposes. We are committed to user privacy protection and will keep everything secure as stated in the Data Protection Act, 1984. 

## Third Party Sites

AccessPlace links to other sites in order to provide you with additional useful information and services. Third party Internet sites and services accessible through AccessPlace have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. AccessPlace has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. We encourage you to look for and review the privacy policies of any third-party site you visit. 

## AccessPlace Quotes

The AccessPlace Quotes service is provided via a third party, ServiceMagic.co.uk. When you fill out a quote form on AccessPlace the information goes through to ServiceMagic.co.uk who pass it on to their approved contractors in order to provide you with the best possible quote. ServiceMagic.co.uk's privacy policy can be found here

## Standard User Data

The standard data we collect about our users is Non-Personally Identifiably Information, meaning it is not information which identifies them as an individual. By using any of AccessPlace services or reading its content, you agree that you understand the nature of this data collection. 

When you log onto AccessPlace, certain Non-Personally Identifiably Information is normally collected by our servers. This information may include, but may not be limited to, the location or website from which you came, the time you spend on parts of AccessPlace or its related sites, the software you use to browse the Internet (for example Netscape or Microsoft Internet Explorer), the amount of information you access from AccessPlace and quantity of pages downloaded. This data collection is standard and common to most websites on the Internet. 

This information does not identify you as an individual, and none of this information will be disclosed in any form that is specific to you as a user of AccessPlace, unless otherwise stated. AccessPlace may disclose this Non-Personally Identifiably Information to trusted, industry regulated, third party partners. These partners may use the Non-Personally Identifiably Information to show you advertising that is more relevant and interesting to you. 

## Cookies

AccessPlace use cookies to better provide our services and information. On the Internet, a "cookie" is a file that a website transfers to a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. This is a common feature of many websites on the Internet, and is employed by AccessPlace to better serve to you our services and content. The cookies only collect Non-Personally Identifiably Information. 

## Third Party Ads

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.

## Further Policy

It is an AccessPlace policy that we will not disclose Personally Identifiably Information you may choose to submit to AccessPlace to any third parties. We follow a strict policy of no 'spam' and no sales of Personally Identifiably Information. 

## Opt Out

You may choose to opt out of the collection or use of Personally Identifiable Information by not providing your name or email address when you contact us and/or contacting us and ask us to remove your personal information from our database. 

You may choose to opt out of the collection or use of Non-Personally Identifiably Information by turning off cookies in your browser settings and/or visiting http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices to opt-out of customised ads by our partner sites.

## Children

We welcome users of all ages to our content and services. If you are under the age of thirteen (13), we do, however, specifically request that you have the permission of your parents or legal guardian to view any content at AccessPlace and to take part in any and all services we offer, as we cannot and will not be held responsible for any information received or disclosed by our users. 

## User Consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and uses of the information detailed here. Any changes in our Privacy Policy will appear on this page so you are aware of what we collect and how we use it. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.accessplace.com/about.htm#contact).
